



sofievandenbrand@live.nl



21-09-1996



Torenallee 303

5617BR Eindhoven

## ABOUT ME

Outside of studying for my master's degree and working at the department of methodology and statistics, I enjoy bouldering and rock climbing. If the weather and time allow it, I would like to get more experience in hiking and climbing mountains.

## Skills

Organization:

Programming in R:

SPSS:

Cooperation:

English

#### Sofie van den Brand

# Experience

Student assistant M&S 2018-present

As a student assistant at the department of Methodology and Statistics I have been involved in several smaller jobs at the department:

- Assisting in the development of the ASReview project | 2020 present
- Assistant organizer of S4 conference which will be held in 2021 due to Covid-19 | 2019 present
- Student assistant during the summer school course on missing data | 2019
- Assistant organizer of the Summer School courses | 2019
- Teaching first year undergraduate statistics workgroups | 2018-2019
- Supervising and teaching software labs for SPSS in several courses | 2018

### Education

Master's degree Methodology and Statistics

Utrecht University | 2019 - present

Bachelor's degree pedagogical sciences

Utrecht University | 2019

Junior year

Southside High school, Alabama | 2015

Gymnasium diploma

Valuascollege Venlo | 2014